<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiment | Ying-Chu Chen&#39;s CV website</title>
    <link>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/tags/experiment/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://yingchuchentw.github.io/tags/experiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Experiment</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 14:30:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url>
      <title>Experiment</title>
      <link>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/tags/experiment/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Those optimized experiment procedure &amp; conduction all begin with details.</title>
      <link>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2022_03_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 14:30:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2022_03_20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Those optimized experiment procedure &amp;amp; conduction all begin with details.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The most outstanding self-learning community</title>
      <link>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2022_01_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 14:30:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2022_01_11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we accept the most outstanding self-learning community award in university of Taipei with profound gratitude. In addition, we can&amp;rsquo;t describe how honored we are to receive this award!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most import of all, we will accept the prize as a tribute to &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Yu-Kai Chang&lt;/strong&gt; (Research Chair Professor, Department of Physical Education and Sport Sciences, National Taiwan Normal University), &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Ching-Feng Cheng&lt;/strong&gt; (Professor, Department of Athletic Performance, National Taiwan Normal University), &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Yi-Hung Liao&lt;/strong&gt;  (Professor, Department of Exercise and Health Science, National Taipei University of Nursing and Health Sciences), and &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Hsin-Fu Lin&lt;/strong&gt; (Professor, Sport Facility Management and Health Promotion, National Taiwan University). Thank you all for novel and marvelous speech!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While this award is being given to me, as a matter of fact, it should go to our team of colleagues and PI, &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Chung-Yu Chen&lt;/strong&gt; (Professor &amp;amp; Director of R&amp;amp;D office, Department of Exercise and Health Sciences, University of Taipei), without whom none of this would have been possible! Let&amp;rsquo;s keep moving forward with strong and active faith in exercise science, sport science, and health science!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The role</title>
      <link>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2021_12_29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 18:11:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2021_12_29/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a practitioner in exercise science, &lt;strong&gt;mindset&lt;/strong&gt; is very important! We are not only the &lt;strong&gt;experiment conductor&lt;/strong&gt; but also the &lt;strong&gt;participant&lt;/strong&gt; sometimes instead. Both roles all lead to the the central role of exercise science. How we balance these two role might be the issue for featured research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As professor Liao always reminds us that: “Something very small or minor can be indicative of something much more important.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other words, an experiment is not just an experiment, it’s about how well  you organize and prepare for the oncoming difficulty and possible defeat. Life isn’t all sunshine and rainbows, how much we can take the challenge and keep moving forward would be the key!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiment Note</title>
      <link>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2021_12_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 18:11:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yingchuchentw.github.io/post/2021_12_01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Liao always reminds us that: “Something very small or minor can be indicative of something much more important.” In other words, an experiment is not just an experiment, it’s about how well  you organize and prepare for the oncoming difficulty and possible defeat. Life isn’t all sunshine and rainbows, how much we can take the challenge and keep moving forward would be the key!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
